虚幻引擎 流行的游戏开发平台
Unreal Engine, a popular game development platform
刚刚推出了一项令人惊叹的新功能
just dropped something truly insane.
它拥有令人惊叹的众多功能
It is chock full of absolutely amazing features.
而这就是所有功能中最出色的
And this is the best of them all.
它的名字是Megalite
It is called Megalite.
接下来 让我们来看看这个令人兴奋的功能集合
Then we look at this insane collection of features that are in the works.
Megalite可以利用这些创造虚拟世界
Megalites can create virtual worlds with these.
哇 这是真的吗？
Ooh, am I seeing correctly?
我简直不敢相信！
I cannot believe it!
这些光源有着细腻的纹理 优雅地为环境添彩
These are textured aerial lights beautifully coloring their surroundings
而我另一个最爱的则是那柔和的阴影
and my other favorite, beautiful soft shadows.
好的 我们知道这过程非常漫长 之前也是这样
Okay, we know that this takes forever, as previously
我们之前需要进行一个非常慢的光线模拟
we needed to run a super slow light simulation for this
并等待这些讨厌的噪音消除
and wait for all this nasty noise to clean up.
这需要多长时间？
So, how long does this take?
嗯 这个并不是提前计算的
Well, this was not computed in advance, yes
你现在看到的就是实时运行的效果
you are seeing it running in real time.
太震撼了！
That is mind-blowing.
哇！
Wow.
现在 我只需要一台能够运行这个的电脑
Now, I just need a PC that would be able to run this thing
那么我们就进入这个黑市吧
so let's enter this shady marketplace.
他们可能在卖掉某些灰色来源的Nvidia显卡
Perhaps they are selling Nvidia cards that have fallen off the truck.
这可不容易找
They are not easy to come by.
我们买一个试试吧
Let's buy one.
嗯 等一下
Hmm, wait a minute.
这个市场一点儿都不阴险
This marketplace is not shady at all.
这里的灯光很多 十分绚丽
There are many beautiful lights
但总感觉缺少了什么
but something is missing.
那究竟缺少了什么？
What is missing?
当然 要有合理的阴影计算
Of course, a proper computation of shadows.
那么 现在打开它
And now, turn it on, yes
现在我们有了一个真正的阴暗市场
we got a proper shady marketplace now.
我出生在共产主义的匈牙利 信不信？
I can tell, I was born in communist Hungary, trust me.
现在重点是 各种闪烁的灯光和油灯随处可见
Now, the point is that there are all kinds of flickering lights, oil lamps
可想而知 灯光真的是多得不可思议
everything that you can imagine, So many lights
艺术家们不必再担心减少灯光
because the artists don't have to worry about cutting lights
来保证游戏流畅
to make the game run well.
就把所有东西都塞进去
Just cram everything in there.
有点像期末考一样
Kind of like a final exam.
好 我们可以开始了
And there we go.
现在 学者们 把你们的纸拿稳
Now, hold on to your papers, fellow scholars
看看有多少啊
and look at how many there are.
哇 太神奇了！
Wow.
超过一千个光源！
Over 1000 light sources
每个光源都为场景投下独特的阴影
each casting their own shadows onto the scene.
就像一场更酷炫的文艺派对
It's like a rave, but nerdier.
彻底颠覆了游戏的规则！
A complete game changer.
而且 这还不止于此
But not only that
虚幻引擎还应用于电影、广播、
Unreal is also used in the movie industry, broadcasting,
产品可视化等各个领域 真是无所不包！
product visualization, you name it.
与他们的模拟引擎结合
Pair it up with their simulation engine
简直完美！
which is also chef's kiss
这就是一个精彩绝伦的组合！
and you have an incredible package.
这些结果真是太惊艳了
These results are so beautiful
我简直不敢相信 我的眼睛都要看呆了
I thought my eyes are going to fall out.
但说真的 发生了什么事情啊？
But seriously, what is happening?
差不多一年内
In approximately a year
他们展示了Nanite 能让游戏拥有惊人的细节
they showcased Nanite for insane level geometry for games
接着是Lumen 带来了真实的反射 这在一年内就出现了两个光影领域的圣杯
and then Lumen for realistic reflections, two Holy Grails in one year
现在再加上Megalights 就变成三项了！
and now with Megalights, make it three.
这些动态灯光竟然能够实时渲染 真是太疯狂了！
It's crazy that these moving lights are rendered in real time.
而且对大多数人来说 这一切竟然都是免费的！
And all this is free for most people.
而且我们还没结束 离完结还差得远呢！
And we are not done yet, not even close.
我特别注意到的九件事
Here are 9 things that really caught my eye.
1.
他们的动画引擎能让角色与几何形状完美结合
Their animation engine adapts these characters to geometry so well
甚至可以用来制作跑酷模拟
you can even make a parkour simulation with it
看看这些角色吧
and look at them
你甚至无需为他们的保险担心
you don't even need to pay their insurance premiums.
2. 变形制作如今更加简单快捷
2. Making deformations are now so much easier and quicker.
3.
你不仅可以扭曲空间 还能扭曲时间 从而更好地编辑动画
You can not only warp space, but time too for better editing of animations.
4. 角色自定义如今无与伦比
4. Character customization is now second to none.
从加州沙滩风格到赛博朋克再到黄仁勋风格 各种选择应有尽有
Where we go from California Beachbody to Cyberpunk to Jensen Huang apparel.
他们还细心处理了许多细节
And they also took care of details
比如自动将裤子塞进靴子
like tucking the pants into boots automatically.
5.
我听你说 卡罗利博士
I hear you say, Dr. Károly
我的模拟效果在哪里？AI又在哪里？
where are my simulations and where is the AI?
好 它就在这里
Well, it is right here.
问吧 学者们 答案就在这里
Ask and you shall receive, fellow scholars.
没错 这里的变形细致到每根肌肉
Yup, here the deformations go down to the level of individual muscles.
太疯狂了！
Insanity.
6.
现在车辆可以定制 不过别太狂哦！
Vehicles can be customized now, but don't go too crazy or ouch.
7. 你还记得这个吗？
7. Remember this?
这不仅仅是一个简单的展示
This was not just a visualization,
而是新款宝马5系的数字副本 配有20,000个零件
but a digital copy of the new BMW 5 Series with 20,000 parts.
我本该说你甚至可以把它打开 可你看看！
I would say you can even pop it open, but look!
这真是世纪的低调表述
Understatement of the century.
连擎天柱都会感到惊艳
Even Optimus Prime would be impressed.
哇 真是惊人！
Wow. 8.
更好的动作捕捉支持 让角色的动作更加真实
Better motion capture support for more realistic character motion.
还有第9个功能
And 9.
这是我最喜欢的功能之一
This is one of my favorites.
通常 创造一个庞大的游戏虚拟世界时
Normally, when you create a vast virtual world for games
一般来说 没有一台服务器能独立应付 但现在
often no one server can deal with it alone, but now
可以将其分配到多个游戏服务器上
you split them up between multiple game servers
玩家从一个区域切换到另一个区域时
and when the players transition from one region to another
这一切都非常无缝
it is so seamless
他们甚至没有察觉到其中的奥妙
they don't even notice the trick.
试想一下
Just think about that.
哎呀 我得开始省点咖啡钱来买它了
Goodness, so I better start cutting down on the coffee budget to buy it.
我可是说的不是BMW哦
I mean, not the BMW
而是能顺利运行这个的新的电脑
but a new PC that can run this.
星巴克 真是消耗PC预算的罪魁祸首
Starbucks, the destroyer of PC budgets.
走开吧
Be gone.
或者说不了
Or not.
我也不知道啊
I don't know.
我可不是美国人
I am not from America.
那么如果还是不够
And if we still don't have enough
至少我可以在这儿用租来的便宜Lambda GPU做一个
at least I can make one here with a cheap, rented Lambda GPU
通过Text2Image
through Text2Image.
哈 赢了！
Ha, checkmate.
现在 你看 哇
And now, look, Ooh
你还没见过真正的东西呢
you haven't seen anything yet.
他们居然还有一份公开的路线图 真是不可思议！
They also have a public roadmap, which is, wow
此时此刻 正在酝酿着许多新事物
an insane amount of things are brewing right as we speak.
你看看这！
Just look at that.
天哪 纸堆成山！
Holy mother of papers.
我最喜欢的三项功能是学习代理
Three of my favorites coming up are learning agents,
超赞的效果 以及更好的昼夜变化
yummy, better day and night sequences,
还有这一项
and then this.
哎呀！
Oh my.
再说一次 大部分功能对我们这些同道是免费的
And once again, all this is free for most of us Fellow Scholars.
这一刻真是太美好了！
What a time to be alive!
如果你受到启发
And if you feel inspired
如果你想在NVIDIA GPU上尝试一些实验 推荐你使用Lambda
and you wish to run your own experiments on NVIDIA GPUs, check out Lambda.
Lambda是一个专为大型人工智能项目设计的云服务
Lambda is a cloud service for large-scale AI projects
这真的是我最喜欢的服务
and it is my absolute favorite.
真的 马上去lambdalabs.com/papers试一下吧！
Seriously, try it out now at lambdalabs.com slash papers
或者直接点击下方的链接
or click the link in the description.
如果你选择使用Lambda
If you use Lambda
你可以在强大的硬件上进行实验
you can run your own experiments on super powerful hardware
同时你还支持了Two Minute Papers
and you also support Two Minute Papers.